Contact

276-696-1163 (Mobile) jonathanmoore@computer.org

www.linkedin.com/in/jdm7dv (LinkedIn) www.mooreenterprises.org (Company)

Top Skills

WPF

C++

Visual Studio

Certifications

ACM Fellow

RSA Fellow

Microsoft Certified Soultions Developer

IEEE Fellow

Honors-Awards

Honor Society

Webby Award

Royal Society Of The Arts Fellowship

Mental Health Wellness

Jonathan Moore

Adobe, Microsoft

Abingdon, Virginia

Summary

I began my professional career right out of high school in technical support and development as a Macromedia User Group then later worked for Adobe and FreeBSD volunteer and contributor. At the same time pursuing my associates and bachelors in computer science .I graduated summa cum laude from Tenn. Tech and a UVa alumni. I was also a web developer for the UVa-Wise Magazine. And Vice President of the ACM Wise Chapter. My complete discography is available on Bandcamp. I'm a BMI writer and publisher. I went to #1 in Ambient on Reverbnation in 2019. And developed some small VST's and Rack Extensions for Reason Studios. I recently became a Microsoft Visual Studio industry partner. I'm in the Virginia and National Associations for the Gifted since 2011 And IEEE Computer Society also a member of the Mensa High IQ society on LinkedIn I also have been a Microsoft MVP. I am wanting to pursue gifted studies at the University of Connecticut maybe. I scored a 140 on the Mensa mobile app. . I'm an INTJ- T top 2 percent of the global population. I'm Irish, German, Ashkenazi Jewish, Mediterranean (Tuscany) and Southwest Asian primate haplogroup's H3G1 and RZ-9.

(R-Z9) H3G1 has a lot of protective alleles. Rare in Eastern Europe and haplogroup mtDNA R is Ashkenazi Jewish but Irish Jewish. and 1.6% Neanderthal And 2.6% Denisovan. Below the National Average of 2.4%.

Moral, Loyal, Educated, Computer Science, Music, and Reading, I am a Moore #1 Irish/British pedigree. and Heritage activist. Microsoft Partner and in Adobe contract. Royal Society of the Arts Fellow. I don't believe in making a persons heritage extinct only forward and extant. And vote Libertarian or Green. I frequently read Burke's Peerage. Finally was awarded my title of nobility from the UK. And I also know society is zero sum and will only go to fairs. I received straight A's in computer science in college at Tenn Tech and a 3.0 at UVa.

I also helped win two Nobel Prizes one for the Higgs Boson and one for Gravitational Waves through BOINC.

I make a sustainable intangible income through copyrights and through cost basis valuation with COCOMO II engineering models.

My National Genographic were done my Roche and Illumina

Experience

Adobe

Software Engineer September 2016 - Present (3 years 7 months)

Reason Studios Software Engineer March 2015 - Present (5 years 1 month)

Rack Extensions and VST's For Reason 10 + Helped develop Complex 1 and a Reason Sound Designer

.NET Foundation
Senior Software Engineer
July 2000 - Present (19 years 9 months)

A Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer In Visual C++ 6.0 and at Microsoft Research in some capacity since 2002, Shared Source Common Language Infrastructure 2.0 now ECMA Standard 335, Trident, IPV6, The GRETA Regular Expression Template Archive, MSDN Operating Systems Subscriber 2005-2006 Microsoft Partner Network and shipped the Office 2007 Ribbon (System.WinForms. Ribbon) and bought Action Pack Subscriber from 2006 - 2010 . Mac Pro And Adobe CS2 Premium in 2008 Using Bootcamp Microsoft Biology Foundation a Bioinformatics Framework for Outercurve under Rick Binge a Microsoft Research Company at UVa and Barrelfish since 2013 on Ubuntu with Haskell and C. At UVa Wise In CLA Contract with Microsoft And a Bizspark Startup from 2014-2019. NET Foundation on a Microsoft Team and member and CLA with Adobe. Working on Brackets And since licensed Detours as an ISV from Microsoft Research. I also have the NT Research Kernel for XP from a College Academic programe. Also obtained Windows

2000 and NT 4.0 Source from UVa in 2000. And A Microsoft Partner with Office 365 Sales from 2007-2011.

Ableton

User Group Organizer October 2017 - 2020 (3 years)

Bandcamp

Computer Music Experimentalist 2015 - 2020 (5 years)

Computer Music Experimentalist and #1 on the Reverbvation in Ireland ambient charts and Microsoft Bizspark Startup now on Hiatus

Broadcast Music, Inc. (BMI) Electronic Musician March 2005 - 2020 (15 years) Abingdon, Va

#1 in Ireland and City of Dublin on the Reverbnation Ambient charts Published by BMI

Northrop Grumman Software Engineer May 2013 - 2013 (less than a year) Lebanon, Virginia

Software Engineering Missile Container Capstone Under Ortero

Macromedia

Technical Support

December 2000 - October 2006 (5 years 11 months)

Macromedia User Group Organizer for the Tri-Cities TN/Va Area. Licensed the SWF Format and Flash Player Sources from the Macromedia Flash Team. Flash Certified Developer.. Then Adobe employee. Macromedia sent 4 care packages including Director 7, Dreamweaver UltraDev, Drumbeat 2000, Flash 4 and Freehand 9 studio Dreamweaver 4 and Fireworks 3 with reviewer guides and demo kits. Then I bought Macromedia Studio MX and Studio 8. for Windows and Mac

Education

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

· (2014 - 2021)

Udemy Academy

Complex Systems Theory, Complex Adaptive Systems, Estate Planning and Trusts. \cdot (2018 - 2021)

The University of Virginia's College at Wise Bachelor of Science, Computer Software Engineering and Digital Ats and Design · (2008 - 2013)

Stanford Online

· (2002 - 2004)

Tennessee College of Applied Technology-Elizabethton Microtechician Diploma, Computer Science · (1999 - 2001)